<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hyperculture</title>
    <link>https://www.hyperculture.site/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hyperculture</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 08:24:11 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.hyperculture.site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Humans</title>
      <link>https://www.hyperculture.site/humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 09:16:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hyperculture.site/humans/</guid>
      <description>Yegwa Ukpo Self Portrait
Yegwa Ukpo is the founder and Head Maintainer at Newtype, a maintenance practice focused on wisdom ecologies of food, shelter, clothing and being; exploring the use of play, playgrounds, storytelling and other indigenous technologies as tools for worldbuilding and the crafting of possible futures.
 Yemi Awosile Portrait by Akemi Kurosaka
Yemi Awosile is a designer living and working in London. Her work is informed by cultural insights expressed primarily through textiles and printed matter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glossary</title>
      <link>https://www.hyperculture.site/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 09:15:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hyperculture.site/glossary/</guid>
      <description>Hyperculture Glossary Concept Overview Please click to download presentation (PDF Format)
 Year Garments One of the signature garments produced by Hyperculture, a year garment can take a variety of forms. What makes any garment a year garment is whether or not it is marked using hypermarks and treated as an object being taken care of for future custodians.
This means that any item of clothing can be called a year garment, and not just clothes designed specifically to be one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primer</title>
      <link>https://www.hyperculture.site/primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 09:14:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hyperculture.site/primer/</guid>
      <description>Hyperculture is a philosophy and community built around an approach to making, taking care of and handling garments and other objects throughout their life and end of life.
Inspired by the fact that in a lot of indigenous cultures, objects were considered to be entities in their own right. With the spirit of the maker said to imbued into exemplary ones. Objects were entangled with the lives of their owners and the times they existed in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.hyperculture.site/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 07:39:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hyperculture.site/projects/</guid>
      <description>The Life of Objects The Life of Objects exhibition was put together by Newtype Studios in collaboration with Yemi Awosile with support from the British Council and Ellen MacArthur Foundation as part of their Circular Design Lab 2019 programme held in November 2019.
The 2019 cohort was comprised of a selection of design practitioners from all over the African continent and focused on how to propagate circular design and economic principles in various countries and sectors throughout Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>